SHRINIVAS CHILKA

OPERATIONS & BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT

Kondwa Budruk, Pune

+91 9923954222

chilkashri@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

An highly skilled individually with 7+ years of experience in operations & Business development, with a key focus on strong analytical, problem solving, handling situations, best negotiations with customers and organizational abilities. Using my experience and skills to enhance the business as well as achieve the organization goals in an exponential format.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Sales Management Business Development Leadership skills Interpersonal skills

Critical thinking Negotiation Time management Creativity

TECHNICAL SKILL

CRM Excel Windows powerpoint

Sales Force Budgeting Power BI Analytics

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Manager.

Ankekshan Consulting Pvt. Ltd

September 2023 – Till Date.

- New business development involving prospect development.
- Research and build relationships with new clients in corporate.
- Plan approaches and pitch for corporate. Work with a team to develop proposals that speak to the client's needs, concerns and objectives.
- Strengthen the company's direct sales and business development capabilities.
- Run targeted sales & marketing campaigns for business development.
- Work with the content team to understand what sales & marketing collateral can make the business development process stronger.

Sales Manager.

Ixsight Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Pune.

March, 2023 – June 2023

- Handled team of 4 people, Role was to monitor and sync up with team on providing them leads on their cold messaging approaches and client conversion.
- Setting up meeting for demo and presentation with some of the top bank's Like Axis Bank, Mahindra group, IndusInd bank and multiple NBFC's.
- Managing customer through the entire process form cold messaging to final quotation including helping out through POC, signing NDA, and other corporate activities.

Territory Manager IDFC First bank, Pune

- Handled domestic loans and partnered with multiple universities
- Responsible for on boarding clients on digital platform and other non-branch channels.
- Responsible for audit checks for all branch operation
- Accountable to maintain relationship with potential and existing client in order to enhance rapport building and retention.

Sr. Business development executive

UNACADEMY, Bangalore(Remote)

May 2020 - April 2022

- Created and lead a team which acted as a loan desk between Finical firms and Unacadmey's upcoming subscriber.
- Managed team of 5 people helping more than 1000 clients help them become UNACAMDEY premimum member.
- Data analysis and Data Mining of Prospects with an expertise in customer relationship management (CRM) System
- Maintaining relationship with financial institutes and KYC scrutiny.

Senior Relationship officer (Lead-Pune City) Gyandhan, Delhi

Feb 2018-Jan 2019

- As a Senior relationship Officer, acted as a mediator between SBI and BOB Bank. Taking care of all secured product which come under EL.
- Managed a team for 4 professional with them secured loans.
- Giving a detailed understanding about product and allied information to clients.
- · Successfully partnered with big clients in Pune.

Business Development execute AVANSE Financial Services, Pune

Jan 2017-Oct 2017

- Managing and maintaining relations with educational Firms and bringing business from their end.
- To handle end to end activities i.e login to disbursal by coordinating with various departments within the system
- Data mining and schedule the appointments with the clients and concern person of prospective clients.

Business Development Executive

Terwadia Capitals Services, Ahmednagar

Sept 2014 – Dec 2016.

- Managed more than 80 clients and provided financial solutions
- Handling clients via providing recommendations & Trading related services.
- Recommendation of various mutual funds schemes to clients based on their requirements.
- Analyzing financial statements of various companies and recommend these stocks to HNI clients.

EDUCATION

Master in Business Administration

Dr. Babsaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad.

2017

Bachelor in Science

Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad

2015

Personal Details: DOB: 21 Jan 1990 Gender: Male

Language: Marathi, Hindi, English telagu

Permanent Address: N-9, L-11/2, Shivaji Nagar Cidco Aurangabad

Declaration: I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is correction up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the above mentioned particulars.

Place:	
Date :	Shrinivas Chilka.